The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Brother Wang,
the teams we sent to the other countries are gradually returning.
This war was prepared meticulously.
It was beyond our imagination.
We asked eight rank 4 cultivations countries for help,
but almost all of them refused.
Even when our envoys were recieved,
they did not agree to send any troops.
Only a country which has been a friend for generations,
told us out of sympathy,
that their ancestors had made a deal
and issued the order that no one is to help the Four Sect Alliance
How can Xue Yue, a rank 4 country,
have such an influence ?
The real reason for this war is actually
a woman from Xue Yue.
This woman
has only cultivated 100 years.
She has never consumed any pill,
and already has reached Soul Formation.
It's rumored that
she has a never seen before 5 elements constitution.
She was born with 5 elemental spirits guarding her.
Now she controls them.
She is the most talented person born on Suzaku in the past 10 000 years.
This woman,
has attracted the attention of the rank 6 country of Suzaku
which invited her to join them to rule the planet.
She only set a single condition to her joining Suzaku.
Which is to raise Xue Yue to a rank 5 country
and have them leave
the barren North.
The place she chose,
was the Four Sect Alliance.
Four Sect Alliance
On top of that,
The Rain Cauldron of Xue Yue
suddenly appeared in the Four Sect Alliance.
There will be
many powerful Soul Formation cultivators in this war.
My cultivation is still limited.
If I really need to fight them
my only chance is to place one last restriction on this flag
to summon a tribulation.
1 year later
Within 80 feet of the Sky-Locking Nail,
using artifacts is forbidden.
Pay attention !
By order of the sect leader,
take the Green Jade Bell of the Water Ink Sect,
and use it as the center of the formation.
Fellow cultivators,
build the formation with me.
Yes !
Master,
the dragon soul is in place.
It can be woken up at any time.
They have arrived.
Fellow cultivators of Xue Yue,
since you are here for the Rain Cauldron,
it's right here.
Can our two countries call a truce
and let the mortals
survive ?
Kill !
This land
now belongs to Xue Yue.
The Rain Cauldron
also belongs to Xue Yue.
The mortals
will also belong to Xue Yue if they survive.
Kill them now.
This land
is our new Xue Yue.
The cultivators of Xue Yue use this snow for their spells.
It snowed for many years...
so that's why.
Humans
cannot live without a home,
and we, cultivators,
are also human.
If we want to save our homeland,
then today,
we will fight to the death !
Mo Shan\NWater Ink Sect Elder\NMiddle stage Soul Formation
Wu Huichu\NBlack Soul Sect Elder\NLate stage Soul Formation
The five elemental spirits ?
Go !
I heard that the five elemental spirits are all Soul Formation.
Today, I finally meet them.
Qing Fu\NGreen Wood Sect Elder,\NMiddle stage Soul Formation
Both sides are still preserving their power.
The Ice Towers !
That means Soul Formation elders have arrived
36 Soul Formation cultivators...
4 of them are Late stage.
Xue Yue sent all of their elders on this battlefield...
Zhou Yun\NBlack Soul Sect Great Elder\NLate stage Soul Formation
I am the Black Soul Sect's Zhou Yun
May I ask if you are Xue Yue's Red Butterfly ?
So it's fellow cultivator Zhou Yun,
one of the nine Late stage Soul Formation of the Four Sect Alliance
I admire you.
The Nine-Sons killing formation is very powerful,
it can definitely kill anyone below Soul Transformation
Although this formation is strong
It will consume the lifespan of Seniors.
If we lose our country,
our sects
and our lives.
What's the point of having preserved our lifespan ?
The key to this battle is Red Butterfly.
Once this woman dies,
Xue Yue will lose the support of the country of Suzaku.
Then we will have a chance to win the war.
Xue Yue could not have overlooked this strategy of yours.
There might be dozens
of Soul Formation cultivators
laying in ambush around Red Butterfly.
to save her no matter what.
What should we do ?
We need to force their Soul Formation cultivators
to put all their efforts into the battlefield.
No matter what it takes.
Fellow cultivators,
let's fight !
Lifespan sacrifice !
Burning away your lifespans ?
Futile.
The damage is spread out ?
Nine-Sons killing formation !
Rise !
Our combined strength,
can kill you !
They killed Red Butterfly ?
This seemed too easy to be real.
Red Butterfly is dead !
The Four Sect Alliance will not give up its land !
We won't give up our land !
Kill them !
Guardian Azure Dragon,
protect our Four Sect Alliance !
So the reason his status is so high
despite only being Nascent Soul
is because he has the bloodline
of the Guardian Azure Dragon.
Red Butterfly is dead,
the five elemental spirits are weakened.
My fellow cultivators, do your best to fight !
Do not let that tiger escape !
Seal !
The elements of the Heaven Defying Bead are incomplete.
Maybe I can absorb this Soul Formation earth spirit.
It's worth trying.
Where can you escape to ?
Well,
even if the earth spirit is injured,
I cannot underestimate its strength.
Evil beast !
Bold of you !
Junior is a disciple of the White Cloud Sect
I am Qing Song's disciple.
My master ordered me to take the earth spirit.
Senior, don't blame me.
It's really Qing Song's passage of time domain.
White Cloud Sect !
If that Soul Formation cultivator were to act,
I would be dead without a doubt.
The restriction flag was damaged.
Snatching food from the tiger's mouth
is too risky.
What's this ?
This ice sculpture is almost impossible to detect with Divine Sense.
It seems that even the Soul Formation cultivators
did not notice it.
The power of ice contained in it is tremendous
It must be a part of a formation.
This ice formation covers the whole Four Sect Alliance.
This war
is far from over.
A gigantic ice formation ?
This is...
a formation ?
Xue Yue came well prepared...
Everyone, be careful !
This is bad...
Lord Envoy,
the country of Suzaku promised
that they would help me once.
So now...
Please kill this Azure Dragon !
Red Butterfly\NXue Yue's genius Dao Child\NPeak Late stage Soul Formation
I've had my share of wounds,\Nnow I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes,\Nfor life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,\Nmy adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer\Nout of reach.
Immortals\Nare obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades\Nseek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself\Nand that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes\Nand awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials\Nto get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,\NI can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done\Nby my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,\NI need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,\Nonly my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.\NEven if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,\Nlike the descent of a god.